# Vitalii Verdiiev, React Front-end Developer

B-Day: May 17, 1992 Email: vitaliiverdiiev@gmail.com Languages:

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine

LinkedIn: <u>vitaliiverdiiev</u>

Phone: +380 63 510 57 69

LinkedIn: <u>vitaliiverdiiev</u>

Telegram: ukrainiancustomer

- Ukrainian (native)

### **Summary:**

Front-end developer with 3 years of commercial experience and over 5 years of coding since late 2018. Seeking engaging projects with an experienced team to learn from and grow. **Prefer projects where my tech stack meets up to 80%** of the requirements, highlighting my eagerness to learn and expand my skills.

## Tech stack:

JavaScript/**TypeScript**, **React**/Next.js, HTML5/CSS3/**SCSS**/LESS, RestAPI/Axios/**TanstackQuery**, GraphQL/ApolloGraphQL, Formik/**ReactHookForm**, Yup/**Zod**, ESLint/Prettier/Husky, Jira/ClickUp **ChakraUI**/MaterialUI/AntDesign/**TailwindCSS**/ShadcnUI, Git, Docker, Linux

### **Experience:**

Front-end Developer at Nuvalt of Uniqit Group LLC (product company)

May 2023 - Jun 2024 (1 year 2 months) - full-time - Kyiv, Ukraine

- Developed features for admin and statistics dashboard apps (Crypto Business Management Platform).
- Worked on a self-hosted installer.
- Translated designs into landing pages within tight deadlines.
- Contributed to the creation of a custom UI library.

#### Front-end Developer at Faster Than Light LLC (outsource/outstaff company)

Oct 2021 - May 2023 (1 year 8 months) - full-time - Kyiv, Ukraine

- Delivered an MVP for the Offsiter project, helping the team secure investments.
- Developed an Accounting page for an internal CRM project, closely collaborating with design, QA, and backend teams.
- Supported multiple projects part-time, ensuring sprint goals were met and delivering high-quality work under tight deadlines.

#### Education:

Front-end Developer (React/TypeScript)

DAN.IT Education, Kyiv, Ukraine Jan 2020 - Aug 2021

**Bachelor's** Degree & **Master** of Business Administration, Management of Organizations and Administrations Donetsk Institute of Tourist Business, Donetsk, Ukraine Sep 2009 - Feb 2015